http://www.pollyklaas.org/about/privacy_disclaimer.html

Talking to Strangers
Why Play "What If..."?
Privacy Policy
The Polly Klaas Foundation is committed to protecting your privacy. To make your experience at our website more convenient, we gather information from you. We maintain the privacy of your information using security technologies and adhere to policies that prevent unauthorized use of your personal information.
What personal information do we collect, and how is it used?
We collect information at various locations on our website that visitors access or visit. We also collect information volunteered by visitors, such as survey information and/or website registrations. Any personal information we collect is used for internal review and is either discarded or used by us to contact our members for purposes such as verifying your mailing address for a product you requested, or contacting you if there is a problem with a donation transaction. We keep confidential all personal information entered during registration.
When we do collect personally identifiable information, it is always voluntarily submitted by you (e.g., when you order a safety kit, volunteer, or request our enewsletter). The information collected is used to send you products you have requested or to email reminders and other information we think will be of interest.
If, for any reason, you would like to be removed from our email list, you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any message we send you or by sending an email to service@pollyklaas.org with "Unsubscribe" in the Subject Line.
We may also monitor and track information such as member usage patterns of our website. We compile this information into a statistical aggregate which we use, together with your personal information, for internal business and administrative purposes including improving our website, our operations and our client service.
Protecting your privacy
As part of our commitment to ensuring the privacy of our users, we never sell or exchange names, email addresses, or any other personally identifiable information about our online members with anyone. We keep confidential any personal information entered during registration, although we may share aggregate information about website usage and traffic patterns, stripped of any personally identifiable information, to third parties to comply with various reporting obligations and for business or marketing purposes. We may also share limited personally identifiable information with third parties on a confidential basis to enable a third party to perform certain tasks for us, such as maintain an email list, conduct a survey or send email alerts and/or newsletters, on our behalf. We require these third parties to honor the same privacy policy we adhere to: never sell or exchange names, email addresses, or any other personally identifiable information about our online members with anyone.
Use of cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that are stored on your computer and are used for record keeping purposes. We use cookies to make visiting and using our website easier. Cookies can help us see which parts of our website are the most or least popular and provide us direction to improve our users' online experience.
Financial Transactions
To process a charitable contribution it is necessary for the Polly Klaas Foundation to gather the visitor's name, email address, mailing address, phone and credit card information. This information is used to verify identity and execute the financial transaction. Additionally, phone number and email address information may be used to contact visitors if there is a problem with the transaction.
If you donate a vehicle or property to the Polly Klaas Foundation information about the donation will be collected in addition to your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address.
The Polly Klaas Foundation may use service providers (merchant banks, ecommerce entities, and other agents) for the express purpose of conducting financial transactions. Personal information is kept private and secure and is not sold rented or traded to third parties. Credit card numbers are used only at the time of the transaction and are not stored following the conclusion of the transaction unless a transaction is selected that occurs on a regular basis. For transactions that recur, limited credit card information (not your complete card number) is stored in an encrypted format.
Links to Other Sites
The Polly Klaas Foundation provides links to several other third party websites as convenience to you. While we make efforts to choose our links carefully, we cannot take any responsibility for the content of linked websites, or for the privacy policies of websites we link to. Since we do not control these websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these third party websites prior to any use. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by www.pollyklaas.org.
Changes to this Policy
Polly Klaas Foundation reserves the right, in its sole discretion and without any obligation , to modify or correct and error or omissions in any portion of the website. If our privacy policy changes at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes. If you are concerened about how your information is being used please check back at our Website periodically.
Contact
For questions regarding this Privacy Policy statement, or the practices of this site please email us at service@pollyklaas.org or contact:
Polly Klaas Foundation, P.O. Box 800, Petaluma, CA 94953, (800) 587-HELP
Disclaimer
The information and recommendations on this website are presented in good faith and believed to be correct. However, Polly Klaas Foundation makes no representations or warranties, either express or implied, as to the completeness, accuracy or timeliness of any of the materials on the Polly Klaas Foundation site, or on any websites which are linked to the Polly Klaas Foundation site. Polly Klaas Foundation also does not make any representations that any information or products mentioned on this site, or in any linked websites, are fit for any particular purpose.
Therefore, the Polly Klaas Foundation will not be responsible, under any circumstances, for damages of any nature resulting from the use of or reliance upon any information from the Polly Klaas Foundation website, or any other website which is linked to the Polly Klaas Foundation website. Links to third party Web sites on this site are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the Polly Klaas Foundation website.
The Polly Klaas Foundation does not conduct testing or certification of any products, services or merchandise, has no control over the content, products, or services provided by the third-party websites and does not endorse any services or products which may be referred to on the Polly Klaas Foundation website.
The Polly Klaas Foundation
Making America Safe for All Children
PO Box 800
Petaluma, CA 94953
Phone: 800-587-4357
Fax: 707-769-4019
E-mail: service@pollyklaas.org
Site Policies
